Using the right services involves considering their cost and level of redundancy.
使用正确的服务涉及考虑其成本和冗余程度
This combination can make for odd trade-offs.
这种组合可以做奇怪的权衡取舍
For example, you might be better off running
例如 您可以更好地运行
the same lambda function in two different regions than have the same work done twice.
两个不同区域的 lambda 函数的工作时间比两次相同
This could be far cheaper than trying to run
这可能比尝试运行更便宜
another service in a multi-region configuration.
多区域配置中的另一个服务
Once you are familiar with a wide array of AWS services,
一旦您熟悉广泛的 AWS 服务
you can use your knowledge of their multi-AZ or
你可以用自己的多 AZ 或
multi-region abilities to select services to achieve your platform's availability needs.
选择服务以实现平台的可用性需求的多区域能力
As Dr. Sue says,
正如苏医生所说
"Think left and think right,
" 左右思考
and think low and think high.
好好想想
Oh, the things you can think up if only you try."
哦 只要你努力就能想到的事情  "